Guide to the Edward M. Bassett papers, 1892-1948
Bassett, Edward M. papers, 1892-1948
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Edward M. Bassett papers, 1892-1948
2708
Edward M. Bassett, 1863-1948.
16.3 cubic ft.
Correspondence, books, articles, reports, legal briefs transcripts, books, and scrapbooks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, books, articles, reports, legal briefs transcripts, and scrapbooks dealing with Bassett's tenure as a U.S. Congressman, 1902-1905, and his membership on committees and boards including the Public Service Commission of New York, the Brooklyn Committee on City Plan, the Zoning Committee of the City of New York, and the Regional Plan of New York and Its Environs Committee. Papers deal primarily with zoning and city planning in New York City. Also includes many articles, reports and books authored by Bassett, such as The Master Plan, Zoning, and the Autobiography of Edward M. Bassett.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Bassett was a United States congressman, 1902-1905, and served on the Public Service Commission of New York, during which time he aided in the development of the dual subway plan in New York City. He was vice-chairman of the Brooklyn Committee on City Plan, whose report was published in 1914; chairman of the Heights of Buildings Commission in New York City, whose final report, 1916, presented the first Zoning Resolution of the City of New York, also the first comprehensive zoning ordinance in the United States. Most of his work, both private and on committees, concerns city planning, zoning and the legal issues surrounding these fields.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, books, articles, reports, legal briefs transcripts, and scrapbooks dealing with Bassett's tenure as a U.S. Congressman, 1902-1905, and his membership on committees and boards including the Public Service Commission of New York, the Brooklyn Committee on City Plan, the Zoning Committee of the City of New York, and the Regional Plan of New York and Its Environs Committee. Papers deal primarily with zoning and city planning in New York City. Also includes many articles, reports and books authored by Bassett, such as The Master Plan, Zoning, and the Autobiography of Edward M. Bassett. There are also extensive legal records concerning zoning laws, regulations, and questions throughout the United States. Among his numerous correspondents were Harland Bartholomew, Otto M. Eidlitz, Lawson Purdy, Nelson P. Lewis, George McAneny, John Purroy Mitchel, Lewis H. Pounds, Frederic B. Pratt, Lewis T. Reed, Charles W. Shelton, Walter Stabler, Alfred T. White, and Robert H. Whitten.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bassett, Edward M. (Edward Murray), 1863-1948.; Bassett, Edward Murray, 1863-1948. Master plan.; Bassett, Edward Murray, 1863-1948. Zoning.; Bassett, Edward Murray, 1863-1948. Autobiography of Edward M. Bassett.; Brooklyn Committee on City Plan.; New York (N.Y.). Heights of Buildings Commission.; New York (N.Y.). Zoning Committee.; New York (State). Public Service Commission.; Regional Plan of New York and Its Environs.; United States. Congress.
Subjects:
City planning-New York (State).; Politics, Practical.; Zoning.
Places:
New York (N.Y.)--City planning.; Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)--City planning.
Form and Genre Terms:
Autobiographies.; Scrapbooks.; Transcripts.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Available Copies:
Microfilm available for correspondence files, subject files, and scrapbooks. Boxes 1-5 contained copies of outgoing correspondence on very brittle paper and were discarded after filming. Box 6, incoming correspondence, was filmed and kept. Boxes 7-10 were filmed and kept. Boxes 11-16 were not filmed. Brittle scrapbooks in Boxes 17-22 were filmed and discarded. Box 23 was not filmed.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Outgoing correspondence
Previously in Boxes 1-5 and now available on Microfilm only.
Series II. Incoming correspondence
Box 6 (Also available on Microfilm.)
Series III. Zoning files
Boxes 7-14 (Boxes 7-10 are also available on Microfilm.)
Series IV. Scrapbooks
Previously in Boxes 17-22 and now available on Microfilm only.
Series V. Published materials
Boxes 15-16
CONTAINER LIST
- Outgoing correspondence
  Materials previously stored in Boxes 1-5 are now available on Microfilm only.
  - Abercrombie, R.G., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abraham and Straus, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academy of Music, 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ackerman, Christine, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Ackerman, Frederick L., 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Acme Foundry Company, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Addams, Charles, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albrecht, Christina, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alden, Edmund K., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alden, Edmund K., 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Allen, Alice W., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Allen, Alice W., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Allen, Joseph, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Allis, Frederick S., 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Alvord, Dean, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "The American City", 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 15a)
  - American Linoleum Manufacturing Company, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Linoleum Manufacturing Company, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Ammerman, Benjamin, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Anderson, Oressa, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Archibald, Charles H., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Archibald, Ruth H., 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arkwright Club, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Arlington Stamp Company, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Armstrong, J.C., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Armstrong, Phoebe F., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Armstrong, Phoebe F., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arnold, Bion J., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Arnstein, L., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Arrowsmith, H., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Arthur, U.N., 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Atlantic National Bank of the City of New York, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Attorney's National Clearing House Co., 1914 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Atwater, Clara W., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Atwater, Clara W., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Atwater, Elsie W., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Atwater, Elsie W., 1914 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Atwater, Elsie W., 1915 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Atwater, Elsie W., 1922 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Atwater, Elsie W., 1923 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Atwater, Elsie W., 1924 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Atwater, Elsie W., 1925 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Atwater, John A. and Atwater, Elsie W., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Atwater, William C., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Atwater, William C., 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Auerbach, Meyer, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Austin, Annie K., 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Austin, George E., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - General A Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - General A Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - General A Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - General A Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - General A Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - General A Correspondence, 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Babbott, Frank L., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Babbott, Frank L., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Babbott, Frank L., 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Bailey, Harold J., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Bailey, William F., 1914 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Ballantyne, D.L., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Ballenberger, Otto F., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Ballow, A.E., 1912 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Ballow, Mrs. Christina, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Balsley, Rena R., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Bank of America, Atlantic Office, 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Barber, R.M., 191-1912 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Barber R.M., Esq., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Bardwell and Hagenbuch, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Barrett, Miss Martha M., 1911 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Bartholomew, Harold, 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Bartley, Susan D., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Bartley, Susan D., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Bassett, Mrs. Annie P., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Bassett, Mrs. Annie P., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Bassett, Mr. and Mrs. C.R., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Bassett, Hon. Edward M., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Bassett, Hon. Edward M., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Bassett, Elvira R., 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Bassett, Emily I., 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Bassett, Mr. and Mrs. George B., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Bassett, Helen P., 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Bassett, Isabel, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Bassett, Miss Marion P., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Bassett, Preston R., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Bates, Nay and Abbott, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Baumann, Elizabeth, 1923-1924 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Baylies, Edmund L., 1911 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Bay State Collection Agency, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Bedell, Edwin J., 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Behrens, Mrs. H.F., 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Bell, Will J., 1912 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Bell, Johnson A., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Benedict, G.S., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Benedict, G.S., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Benedict, G.S., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Benedict, Lorenzo, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Benedict, Lorenzo, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Benedict, Lorenzo, 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Benedict, Miss Mary L., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Benedict, Russell, 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Benjamin and Johnes, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Bennett, E.H., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Bennett, J.M., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Bernheimer, Charles L., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Bernstein, Dora, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Bianco, Frank, 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Bingley, Mrs. A.E., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Binkerd, Robert S., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Binkerd, Robert S., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Birmingham, Jennie, 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Blackman, Charles M, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Blair, Mrs. Cora L., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Blair, Mrs. Cora L., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Blair, Grace K., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Blair, Mariana, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Blair, Mariana, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Bleidorn, Mrs. Lena, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Bleidorn, Mrs. Lena, 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Blum, Mr. Edward C., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Bohne-McLaughlin Co., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Bolles, Mr. and Mrs. Charles E., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Bonta, L.R., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Boos, Charles, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Borggreve, Frederick, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Bowersox, Katherine S., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Bowmar, Thomas L., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Bowne, Charles D., 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Bowne, Charles D., 1923-1926 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Boyce, Harry R, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Boyce, Harold R., 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Boyce, Harold R., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - Boyton, Rev. Nehemiah, D.D., 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - Bricker, G.W., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Bridgman, Herbert L., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Brighton Heights Development Co., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Broadway Park Place Co., 1922 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Broadway Trust Co., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Brodie, R.G., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Bronner, Myron G., Esq, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Brooklyn Daily Eagle, 1911-1915 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Brooklyn Daily Eagle, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Brooklyn Daily Times, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 140a)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Brooklyn Rapid Transit Co., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Brooklyn Rapid Transit Co., 1914 (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Brooklyn Trust Co., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - Brooklyn Trust Co., 1924-1926 (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - Brooklyn Weekly News, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Brooks, Edwin M., Esq., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Brown, George G., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Brown and Anderson, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - Bruner, Henry M., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - Brush, George W., M.D., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - Buchman, Mrs. Louisa F., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - Buckley, Mrs. Annie, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Buckley, Mrs. Annie, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Bullard, E.G., Esq., 1912 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Bullard, E.G., Esq., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - Bullock, Harry A., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Bureau for the Collection of Assessments and Arrears, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Burkett, Miller and Wagner, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Burkhard, Mrs. Sarah T., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Burkhard, Mrs. Sarah T., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - Burkhard, Mrs. Sarah T., 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - Burlington Watch Co., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Burlington Watch Co., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Burns Bros. Coal Co., 1913 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - Burrell, F.A.M., 1913-1914 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - Burroughs, Paul G., Esq., 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Burroughs, Paul G., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Burtis, Miss Emma J., 19122-1926 (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Burton, Pomeroy, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Burton, Pomeroy, 1913-1918 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - Buttenheim, Harold S., 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - General B Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - General B Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  - General B Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - General B Correspondenc, 1911-1912 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - General B Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - General B Correspondence, 1916-1918 (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - General B Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - General B Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - General B Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Camichel, Mrs. Christine, 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Campbell, John A., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cape May Glass Company, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Carlisle, Hon. John M., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Carmody, Francais X., Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Carney, Mrs. Margaret V., 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Catlin, Mrs. Josephine M., 1915 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Catrevas, Miss Christine, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cauble, Miss. Laura A., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cervadoro, Dominick, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chandler, Prof. C.F., 1912 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - The Chat, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chellew, Walter J., 1912 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chellew, Walter J., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chellew, Walter J., 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chisholm Stationary Co., 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Christen, John, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Citizens Reality and Mortgage Co., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Clark, John G., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Clark, Roscoe N., 1924-1925 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Clerk First District Municipal Court, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Clifton Art Pottery, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Close, Miss Mary, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Cohen, Samuel, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Cohn, Mrs. Rosie, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cohen, Lewis G., M.D., 1922-1924 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Collector of Assessments and Arrears, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Collector of Assessments and Arrears, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Collector of International Revenue, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Collector United States Internal Revenue, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Colonial Adjustment Company, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Coman, Miss Caroline, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Comey, Arthur C., 1923-1925 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Comiskey Realty and Construction Co., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Comiskey Realty and Construction Co., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Commissioner of Finance, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Comstock, James B., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Conant, Samuel D., Esq., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Conant, Samuel D., Esq., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Cogdon, Mrs. Carrie D., 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Congdon, C.W., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Congdon, C.W., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Congregational Church Building Society, 1912 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Congregational Church Building Society, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Connette, E.G., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Connette, E.G., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Connolly, Mrs. Mary T., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Connolly, Hon. Maurice E., 1912 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Connolly, Hon. Maurice E., 1913-1922 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Consolidated Gas Co. of New York, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Cooke, Mrs. Frances M., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Cooke, Robert G., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Cornell, Mrs. Maria L., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Corwin Agency, 1922-1924 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Coward, J.S., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cowles, Mrs. Anna A., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Cowles, Mrs. Anna A., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Cox, Archibald X., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Cox, Thomas V., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Cox, Thomas V., 1924-1926 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Cox, Mrs. Stanley C., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Crabbs, Clarence L., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Cranford, Frederic L., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Cranford, Walter V. and Cranford Company, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Credit Adjustment Co., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Creditors Association Inc., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Creighton, John B., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Creighton, John B., 1915-1923 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Crescent Athletic Club, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Crist, Professor H.M., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Crist, Harris M., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Cromwell, Hon. George, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Cromwell, Hon. George, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Cromwell, Hon. Foster, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Crowley, Geo F. and Co., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Curtain Supply Co., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Cushman, Avery F., Esq., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - General C Correspondence, 1892-1912 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - General C Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - General C Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - General C Correspondence, 1913-1912 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - General C Correspondence, 1913-1912 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - General C Correspondence, 1913-1912 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - General C Correspondence, 1913-1912 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - General C Correspondence, 1913-1912 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - General C Correspondence, 1913-1912 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - General C Correspondence, 1913-1918 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - General C Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - General C Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - General C Correspondence, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - General C Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - General C Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - General C Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - General C Correspondence, 1922-1932 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Daggett, George F., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Dahlgren, W., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Dakin, Arthur H. Esq., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Dana, Arthur D., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Davis, Miss C.T., 1911-1915 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Davis and Quick, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Day, Joseph P., 1915-1918 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Deal, Mrs. Eva A., 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Deal, William H., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - deBerard, A.J., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Decker, Delbert H., Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Decker, Delbert H., Esq., 1915 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - de Forest, Henry P., M.D., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Denbigh, Dr. John H., 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Department of Assessments and Arrears, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Department of Water Supply, Gas and Electricity, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - De Rancy, Henry F., 1914 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Derr, Mrs. Mary F., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Diehl Manufacturing Co., 1914 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Dill, Hohn, Esq., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Ditmas, Charles A., 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Ditmas, Charles A., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Donoho and Co., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Doty, Mrs. Anna L., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Doty, Mrs. Edith M., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Doty, Mrs. Edith M., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Drescher, Alexander S., Esq., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Drewes, F.W., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Driggs, Edmund H., 1912-1914 (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Driver, Mrs. Elizabeth T., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Duffy, Mrs. Ella J., 1914 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - Duncan, Alfred C., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Duncan, W.E., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 127)
  - Dunn, Wareen H., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 128)
  - Dutcher, Abram S., 191 (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - General D Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - General D Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - General D Correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 132)
  - General D Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - General D Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 134)
  - General D Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 135)
  - General D Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - General D Correspondence, 1912-1922 (Box 2, Folder 137)
  - General D Correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - General D Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - General D Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - General D Correspondence, 1922-1939 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - Eastmond, Hohn E., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Ecklsbecker, Frank W., 191 (Box 2, Folder 143)
  - Edsall, James M., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - Edwards, Rev. Chauncey T., D.D., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Eidlitz, Otto M., 1916-1918 (Box 2, Folder 146)
  - Ellerhusen, Ulrich H., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 147)
  - Ellery, Mrs. Mildred Whiton, 1923-1926 (Box 2, Folder 148)
  - Ellett, James T., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 149)
  - Elliott, Gilbert, Esq., 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Ellison, J.M., 1913 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Equitable Trust Company, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Ericksen, Charles F., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Ericksen, Charles F., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - Ericsson, Harriot and Gustaf S., 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Ermold, George and Co., 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 156)
  - Estate of Otto Huber, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 157)
  - Estate of Louise Hutchins, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 158)
  - General E Correspondence, 1911-1915 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - General E Correspondence, 1913-1915 (Box 2, Folder 160)
  - General E Correspondence, 1922-1926 (Box 2, Folder 161)
  - Falkinburg, Messers. John N. and Nelson H., 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 162)
  - Farmers Trust and Loan Co., 1914 (Box 2, Folder 163)
  - Farmers Trust and Loan Co., 1925-1926 (Box 2, Folder 164)